(Leonard(on phone):)Got it.
(Vet:)Should have been a dentist.
OK, what was the best four-ten-four
US locomotive over built?
(Sheldon:)Trick question.
There never was one.
(Man:)-Or was there?
-What?!
(Man:)In 1944, the Pacific Railroad
built number 6131,
(Man:)which rearranged
the drivers and cylinders,
(Man:)solving the problem of the Q-1,
(Man:)creating a duplex-drive
four-four-six-four.
(Sheldon:)In what world is a
four-four-six-four a four-ten-four?
A world I don't want to live in!
(Howard:)Seriously, I no longer want
to live in this world.
(Man:)Hold on to your conductor's hat.
You crank the second and third axles,
(Man:)creating a pair of
internal connecting rods,
and boom! Four-ten-four.
If you think about it,
(Man:)the Q-2 was like the four-ten-four
America never made.
(Sheldon:)I may never stop thinking about it.
(Sheldon:)Amy, what are the odds
we run into this guy?
(Waiter:)Better than you think.